Madam, today Panipuri is free but
what is the condition? You have to eat ten
Panipuris. If I eat one more than ten, I will have to
pay 200 rupees. Oh, if I eat more than
ten,
why are you tensed about it? Baby, when you
were eating, I didn't count everything. Okay,
brother, give it to me. Okay, Madam.
[Music]
Baby, it's 10. No, Madam, yours is 11
Panipuris. That's what I
ate. My mother-in-law counted. No,
Madam, it's 11. No, I counted
correctly. My mother-in-law counted. Wait
a minute. Look here. There is a camera. I
will bring the recorded video footage.
Bring it. What's that? Baby, you didn't count.
No, Baby, I counted correctly.
Look, Madam, the video footage has arrived.
You yourself have to check
[Music] and say, "
You ate that much."
Look, something is wrong with you,
baby, look, give me 200 rupees,
I'll send you a video, edit it a little bit and
send it, okay?